[
 {
	"QuestionID" : 320,
	"Question" : "What is (5 + 9) X 2 - 6 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (five plus nine) times two minus six times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 28,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by zero before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 and 9, and multiply 2 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 6 and 0 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 9 = 14; Now we have: 14 X 2 - 6 X 0; 14 X 2 = 28; 6 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 28 - 0 = 28"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 321,
	"Question" : "What is 51 + 9 X 8 - 5 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is fifty-one plus nine times eight minus five times one?", 
	"Answer" : 118,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and eighteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 475,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by eight and five by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 8 and 5 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 51 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 8 = 72; 5 X 1 = 5; Now we have: 51 + 72 - 5; 51 + 72 = 123; Now we have: 123 - 5 = 118"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 322,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 6 X (1 + 8) + 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus six times (one plus eight) plus two?", 
	"Answer" : 62,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 110,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by the sum of one and eight before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 and 8, and multiply 6 by that sum. Then add 6 to that product, and then add 2 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 8 = 9; Now we have: 6 + 6 X 9 + 2;  6 X 9 = 54; Now we have: 6 + 54 + 2; 6 + 54 = 60; Now we have 60 + 2 = 62"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 323,
	"Question" : "What is 66 + 9 X 5 - 6 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is sixty-six plus nine times five minus six times two?", 
	"Answer" : 99,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 363,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by five and six by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 5 and 6 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 66 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 5 = 45; 6 X 2 = 12; Now we have: 66 + 45 - 12; 66 + 45 = 111; Now we have: 111 - 12 = 99"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 324,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 8) X 2 - 7 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus eight) times two minus seven times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by zero before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 and 8, and multiply 2 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 7 and 0 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 8 = 12; Now we have: 12 X 2 - 7 X 0; 12 X 2 = 24; 7 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 24 - 0 = 24"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 325,
	"Question" : "What is 70 + 7 X 8 - 5 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy plus seven times eight minus five times three?", 
	"Answer" : 111,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and eleven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 601,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by eight and five by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 8 and 5 by 3, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 70 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 8 = 56; 5 X 3 = 15; Now we have: 70 + 56 - 15; 70 + 56 = 126; Now we have: 126 - 15 = 111"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 326,
	"Question" : "What is (1 + 6) X 1 - 5 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (one plus six) times one minus five times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 7,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by zero before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 and 6, and multiply 1 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 5 and 0 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 6 = 7; Now we have: 7 X 1 - 5 X 0; 7 X 1 = 7; 5 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 7 - 0 = 7"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 327,
	"Question" : "What is 58 + 7 X 5 + 9 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is fifty-eight plus seven times five plus nine times four?", 
	"Answer" : 129,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and twenty-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 361,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by five and nine by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 5 and 9 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 58 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 5 = 35; 9 X 4 = 36; Now we have: 58 + 35 + 36; 58 + 35 = 93; Now we have: 93 + 36 = 129"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 328,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 6 X (1 + 7) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus six times (one plus seven) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 55,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 76,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by the sum of one and seven before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 and 7, and multiply 6 by that sum. Then add 3 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 7 = 8; Now we have: 3 + 6 X 8 + 4;  6 X 8 = 48; Now we have: 3 + 48 + 4; 3 + 48 = 51; Now we have 51 + 4 = 55"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 329,
	"Question" : "What is 72 + 5 X 6 - 6 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy-two plus five times six minus six times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 102,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 462,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by six and six by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 6 and 6 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 72 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 6 = 30; 6 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 72 + 30 - 0; 72 + 30 = 102; Now we have: 102 - 0 = 102"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 330,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 5 X (0 + 6) + 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus five times (zero plus six) plus zero?", 
	"Answer" : 34,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 54,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by the sum of zero and six before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 6, and multiply 5 by that sum. Then add 4 to that product, and then add 0 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 6 = 6; Now we have: 4 + 5 X 6 + 0;  5 X 6 = 30; Now we have: 4 + 30 + 0; 4 + 30 = 34; Now we have 34 + 0 = 34"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 331,
	"Question" : "What is 72 + 6 X 7 - 9 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy-two plus six times seven minus nine times four?", 
	"Answer" : 78,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 510,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by seven and nine by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 7 and 9 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 72 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 7 = 42; 9 X 4 = 36; Now we have: 72 + 42 - 36; 72 + 42 = 114; Now we have: 114 - 36 = 78"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 332,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 7 X (2 + 9) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus seven times (two plus nine) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 84,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 114,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by the sum of two and nine before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 and 9, and multiply 7 by that sum. Then add 3 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 9 = 11; Now we have: 3 + 7 X 11 + 4;  7 X 11 = 77; Now we have: 3 + 77 + 4; 3 + 77 = 80; Now we have 80 + 4 = 84"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 333,
	"Question" : "What is 86 + 5 X 7 - 9 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eighty-six plus five times seven minus nine times two?", 
	"Answer" : 103,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 619,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by seven and nine by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 7 and 9 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 86 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 7 = 35; 9 X 2 = 18; Now we have: 86 + 35 - 18; 86 + 35 = 121; Now we have: 121 - 18 = 103"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 334,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 6 X (0 + 8) + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus six times (zero plus eight) plus three?", 
	"Answer" : 53,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 67,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by the sum of zero and eight before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 8, and multiply 6 by that sum. Then add 2 to that product, and then add 3 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 8 = 8; Now we have: 2 + 6 X 8 + 3;  6 X 8 = 48; Now we have: 2 + 48 + 3; 2 + 48 = 50; Now we have 50 + 3 = 53"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 335,
	"Question" : "What is 13 + 9 X 6 - 6 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is thirteen plus nine times six minus six times two?", 
	"Answer" : 55,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 120,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by six and six by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 6 and 6 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 13 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 6 = 54; 6 X 2 = 12; Now we have: 13 + 54 - 12; 13 + 54 = 67; Now we have: 67 - 12 = 55"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 336,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 5) X 2 - 8 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus five) times two minus eight times one?", 
	"Answer" : 10,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ten.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 10,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by one before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 and 5, and multiply 2 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 8 and 1 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 5 = 9; Now we have: 9 X 2 - 8 X 1; 9 X 2 = 18; 8 X 1 = 8; Now we have: 18 - 8 = 10"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 337,
	"Question" : "What is 50 + 6 X 7 - 6 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is fifty plus six times seven minus six times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 92,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 392,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by seven and six by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 7 and 6 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 50 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 7 = 42; 6 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 50 + 42 - 0; 50 + 42 = 92; Now we have: 92 - 0 = 92"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 338,
	"Question" : "What is (5 + 5) X 2 - 7 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (five plus five) times two minus seven times one?", 
	"Answer" : 13,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 13,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by one before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 and 5, and multiply 2 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 7 and 1 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 5 = 10; Now we have: 10 X 2 - 7 X 1; 10 X 2 = 20; 7 X 1 = 7; Now we have: 20 - 7 = 13"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 339,
	"Question" : "What is 33 + 7 X 8 - 9 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is thirty-three plus seven times eight minus nine times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 89,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 320,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by eight and nine by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 8 and 9 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 33 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 8 = 56; 9 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 33 + 56 - 0; 33 + 56 = 89; Now we have: 89 - 0 = 89"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 340,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 9 X (0 + 7) + 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus nine times (zero plus seven) plus one?", 
	"Answer" : 73,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 127,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by the sum of zero and seven before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 7, and multiply 9 by that sum. Then add 9 to that product, and then add 1 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 7 = 7; Now we have: 9 + 9 X 7 + 1;  9 X 7 = 63; Now we have: 9 + 63 + 1; 9 + 63 = 72; Now we have 72 + 1 = 73"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 341,
	"Question" : "What is 31 + 5 X 9 - 7 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is thirty-one plus five times nine minus seven times four?", 
	"Answer" : 48,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 296,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by nine and seven by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 9 and 7 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 31 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 9 = 45; 7 X 4 = 28; Now we have: 31 + 45 - 28; 31 + 45 = 76; Now we have: 76 - 28 = 48"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 342,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 7) X 2 - 5 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus seven) times two minus five times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 22,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by zero before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 and 7, and multiply 2 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 5 and 0 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 7 = 11; Now we have: 11 X 2 - 5 X 0; 11 X 2 = 22; 5 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 22 - 0 = 22"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 343,
	"Question" : "What is 56 + 9 X 7 - 6 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is fifty-six plus nine times seven minus six times three?", 
	"Answer" : 101,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 437,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by seven and six by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 7 and 6 by 3, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 56 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 7 = 63; 6 X 3 = 18; Now we have: 56 + 63 - 18; 56 + 63 = 119; Now we have: 119 - 18 = 101"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 344,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 8 X (1 + 5) + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus eight times (one plus five) plus three?", 
	"Answer" : 59,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 99,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by the sum of one and five before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 and 5, and multiply 8 by that sum. Then add 8 to that product, and then add 3 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 5 = 6; Now we have: 8 + 8 X 6 + 3;  8 X 6 = 48; Now we have: 8 + 48 + 3; 8 + 48 = 56; Now we have 56 + 3 = 59"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 345,
	"Question" : "What is 25 + 5 X 8 - 6 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is twenty-five plus five times eight minus six times four?", 
	"Answer" : 41,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 216,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by eight and six by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 8 and 6 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 25 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 8 = 40; 6 X 4 = 24; Now we have: 25 + 40 - 24; 25 + 40 = 65; Now we have: 65 - 24 = 41"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 346,
	"Question" : "What is 4 + 9 X (3 + 9) + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is four plus nine times (three plus nine) plus three?", 
	"Answer" : 115,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and fifteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 159,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by the sum of three and nine before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 and 9, and multiply 9 by that sum. Then add 4 to that product, and then add 3 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 9 = 12; Now we have: 4 + 9 X 12 + 3;  9 X 12 = 108; Now we have: 4 + 108 + 3; 4 + 108 = 112; Now we have 112 + 3 = 115"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 347,
	"Question" : "What is 79 + 9 X 9 - 5 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy-nine plus nine times nine minus five times two?", 
	"Answer" : 150,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and fifty.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 782,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by nine and five by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 9 and 5 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 79 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 9 = 81; 5 X 2 = 10; Now we have: 79 + 81 - 10; 79 + 81 = 160; Now we have: 160 - 10 = 150"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 348,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 9) X 2 - 9 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus nine) times two minus nine times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 26,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by zero before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 and 9, and multiply 2 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 9 and 0 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 9 = 13; Now we have: 13 X 2 - 9 X 0; 13 X 2 = 26; 9 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 26 - 0 = 26"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 349,
	"Question" : "What is 86 + 6 X 5 - 8 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eighty-six plus six times five minus eight times one?", 
	"Answer" : 108,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 452,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by five and eight by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 5 and 8 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 86 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 5 = 30; 8 X 1 = 8; Now we have: 86 + 30 - 8; 86 + 30 = 116; Now we have: 116 - 8 = 108"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 350,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 9 X (3 + 7) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus nine times (three plus seven) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 99,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 144,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by the sum of three and seven before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 and 7, and multiply 9 by that sum. Then add 5 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 7 = 10; Now we have: 5 + 9 X 10 + 4;  9 X 10 = 90; Now we have: 5 + 90 + 4; 5 + 90 = 95; Now we have 95 + 4 = 99"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 351,
	"Question" : "What is 77 + 9 X 8 - 9 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy-seven plus nine times eight minus nine times four?", 
	"Answer" : 113,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and thirteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 652,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by eight and nine by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 8 and 9 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 77 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 8 = 72; 9 X 4 = 36; Now we have: 77 + 72 - 36; 77 + 72 = 149; Now we have: 149 - 36 = 113"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 352,
	"Question" : "What is (6 + 8) X 3 - 8 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (six plus eight) times three minus eight times two?", 
	"Answer" : 26,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 68,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by two before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 6 and 8, and multiply 3 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 8 and 2 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 + 8 = 14; Now we have: 14 X 3 - 8 X 2; 14 X 3 = 42; 8 X 2 = 16; Now we have: 42 - 16 = 26"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 353,
	"Question" : "What is 77 + 8 X 8 - 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy-seven plus eight times eight minus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 141,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and forty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 680,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by eight and eight by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 8 and 8 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 77 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 8 = 64; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 77 + 64 - 0; 77 + 64 = 141; Now we have: 141 - 0 = 141"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 354,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 6 X (3 + 5) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus six times (three plus five) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 58,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 100,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by the sum of three and five before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 and 5, and multiply 6 by that sum. Then add 6 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 5 = 8; Now we have: 6 + 6 X 8 + 4;  6 X 8 = 48; Now we have: 6 + 48 + 4; 6 + 48 = 54; Now we have 54 + 4 = 58"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 355,
	"Question" : "What is 22 + 6 X 7 - 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is twenty-two plus six times seven minus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 64,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 196,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by seven and eight by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 7 and 8 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 22 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 7 = 42; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 22 + 42 - 0; 22 + 42 = 64; Now we have: 64 - 0 = 64"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 356,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 6) X 4 - 5 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus six) times four minus five times three?", 
	"Answer" : 25,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 105,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by three before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 and 6, and multiply 4 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 5 and 3 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 6 = 10; Now we have: 10 X 4 - 5 X 3; 10 X 4 = 40; 5 X 3 = 15; Now we have: 40 - 15 = 25"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 357,
	"Question" : "What is 78 + 8 X 5 - 5 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy-eight plus eight times five minus five times one?", 
	"Answer" : 113,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and thirteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 425,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by five and five by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 5 and 5 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 78 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 5 = 40; 5 X 1 = 5; Now we have: 78 + 40 - 5; 78 + 40 = 118; Now we have: 118 - 5 = 113"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 358,
	"Question" : "What is (8 + 8) X 3 - 6 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (eight plus eight) times three minus six times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 48,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by zero before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 and 8, and multiply 3 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 6 and 0 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 + 8 = 16; Now we have: 16 X 3 - 6 X 0; 16 X 3 = 48; 6 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 48 - 0 = 48"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 359,
	"Question" : "What is 84 + 5 X 6 - 8 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eighty-four plus five times six minus eight times three?", 
	"Answer" : 90,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 510,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by six and eight by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 6 and 8 by 3, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 84 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 6 = 30; 8 X 3 = 24; Now we have: 84 + 30 - 24; 84 + 30 = 114; Now we have: 114 - 24 = 90"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 360,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 8 X (1 + 7) + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus eight times (one plus seven) plus three?", 
	"Answer" : 69,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 83,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by the sum of one and seven before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 and 7, and multiply 8 by that sum. Then add 2 to that product, and then add 3 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 7 = 8; Now we have: 2 + 8 X 8 + 3;  8 X 8 = 64; Now we have: 2 + 64 + 3; 2 + 64 = 66; Now we have 66 + 3 = 69"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 361,
	"Question" : "What is 26 + 8 X 5 - 7 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is twenty-six plus eight times five minus seven times four?", 
	"Answer" : 38,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 142,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by five and seven by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 5 and 7 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 26 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 5 = 40; 7 X 4 = 28; Now we have: 26 + 40 - 28; 26 + 40 = 66; Now we have: 66 - 28 = 38"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 362,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 7 X (0 + 6) + 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus seven times (zero plus six) plus zero?", 
	"Answer" : 43,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 48,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by the sum of zero and six before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 6, and multiply 7 by that sum. Then add 1 to that product, and then add 0 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 6 = 6; Now we have: 1 + 7 X 6 + 0;  7 X 6 = 42; Now we have: 1 + 42 + 0; 1 + 42 = 43; Now we have 43 + 0 = 43"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 363,
	"Question" : "What is 86 + 6 X 5 + 9 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eighty-six plus six times five plus nine times four?", 
	"Answer" : 152,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and fifty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 496,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by five and nine by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 5 and 9 by 4, and add the second product to the first. Then, add 86 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 5 = 30; 9 X 4 = 36; Now we have: 86 + 30 + 36; 86 + 30 = 116; Now we have: 116 + 36 = 152"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 364,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 5 X (0 + 6) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus five times (zero plus six) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 40,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 70,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by the sum of zero and six before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 6, and multiply 5 by that sum. Then add 6 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 6 = 6; Now we have: 6 + 5 X 6 + 4;  5 X 6 = 30; Now we have: 6 + 30 + 4; 6 + 30 = 36; Now we have 36 + 4 = 40"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 365,
	"Question" : "What is 94 + 6 X 7 - 6 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is ninety-four plus six times seven minus six times three?", 
	"Answer" : 118,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and eighteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 682,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by seven and six by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 7 and 6 by 3, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 94 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 7 = 42; 6 X 3 = 18; Now we have: 94 + 42 - 18; 94 + 42 = 136; Now we have: 136 - 18 = 118"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 366,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 6 X (2 + 7) + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus six times (two plus seven) plus three?", 
	"Answer" : 63,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 111,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by the sum of two and seven before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 and 7, and multiply 6 by that sum. Then add 6 to that product, and then add 3 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 7 = 9; Now we have: 6 + 6 X 9 + 3;  6 X 9 = 54; Now we have: 6 + 54 + 3; 6 + 54 = 60; Now we have 60 + 3 = 63"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 367,
	"Question" : "What is 68 + 6 X 8 - 9 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is sixty-eight plus six times eight minus nine times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 116,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and sixteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 592,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by eight and nine by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 8 and 9 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 68 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 8 = 48; 9 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 68 + 48 - 0; 68 + 48 = 116; Now we have: 116 - 0 = 116"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 368,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 7 X (3 + 8) + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus seven times (three plus eight) plus three?", 
	"Answer" : 81,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 91,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by the sum of three and eight before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 and 8, and multiply 7 by that sum. Then add 1 to that product, and then add 3 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 8 = 11; Now we have: 1 + 7 X 11 + 3;  7 X 11 = 77; Now we have: 1 + 77 + 3; 1 + 77 = 78; Now we have 78 + 3 = 81"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 369,
	"Question" : "What is 43 + 5 X 9 - 6 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is forty-three plus five times nine minus six times four?", 
	"Answer" : 64,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 408,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by nine and six by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 9 and 6 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 43 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 9 = 45; 6 X 4 = 24; Now we have: 43 + 45 - 24; 43 + 45 = 88; Now we have: 88 - 24 = 64"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 370,
	"Question" : "What is (3 + 8) X 3 - 8 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (three plus eight) times three minus eight times two?", 
	"Answer" : 17,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventeen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 50,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by two before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 and 8, and multiply 3 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 8 and 2 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 8 = 11; Now we have: 11 X 3 - 8 X 2; 11 X 3 = 33; 8 X 2 = 16; Now we have: 33 - 16 = 17"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 371,
	"Question" : "What is 98 + 8 X 6 - 9 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is ninety-eight plus eight times six minus nine times three?", 
	"Answer" : 119,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and nineteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 609,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by six and nine by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 6 and 9 by 3, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 98 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 6 = 48; 9 X 3 = 27; Now we have: 98 + 48 - 27; 98 + 48 = 146; Now we have: 146 - 27 = 119"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 372,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 7 X (3 + 6) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus seven times (three plus six) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 76,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 148,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by the sum of three and six before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 and 6, and multiply 7 by that sum. Then add 9 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 6 = 9; Now we have: 9 + 7 X 9 + 4;  7 X 9 = 63; Now we have: 9 + 63 + 4; 9 + 63 = 72; Now we have 72 + 4 = 76"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 373,
	"Question" : "What is 89 + 8 X 8 - 5 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eighty-nine plus eight times eight minus five times two?", 
	"Answer" : 143,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and forty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 766,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by eight and five by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 8 and 5 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 89 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 8 = 64; 5 X 2 = 10; Now we have: 89 + 64 - 10; 89 + 64 = 153; Now we have: 153 - 10 = 143"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 374,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 9) X 2 - 5 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus nine) times two minus five times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 18,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by zero before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 9, and multiply 2 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 5 and 0 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 9 = 9; Now we have: 9 X 2 - 5 X 0; 9 X 2 = 18; 5 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 18 - 0 = 18"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 375,
	"Question" : "What is 20 + 8 X 7 - 5 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is twenty plus eight times seven minus five times four?", 
	"Answer" : 56,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 176,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by seven and five by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 7 and 5 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 20 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 7 = 56; 5 X 4 = 20; Now we have: 20 + 56 - 20; 20 + 56 = 76; Now we have: 76 - 20 = 56"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 376,
	"Question" : "What is (7 + 9) X 4 - 8 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (seven plus nine) times four minus eight times one?", 
	"Answer" : 56,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 56,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by one before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 and 9, and multiply 4 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 8 and 1 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 9 = 16; Now we have: 16 X 4 - 8 X 1; 16 X 4 = 64; 8 X 1 = 8; Now we have: 64 - 8 = 56"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 377,
	"Question" : "What is 70 + 5 X 6 - 9 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy plus five times six minus nine times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 100,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 450,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by six and nine by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 6 and 9 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 70 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 6 = 30; 9 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 70 + 30 - 0; 70 + 30 = 100; Now we have: 100 - 0 = 100"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 378,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 9 X (0 + 7) + 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus nine times (zero plus seven) plus one?", 
	"Answer" : 66,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 78,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by the sum of zero and seven before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 7, and multiply 9 by that sum. Then add 2 to that product, and then add 1 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 7 = 7; Now we have: 2 + 9 X 7 + 1;  9 X 7 = 63; Now we have: 2 + 63 + 1; 2 + 63 = 65; Now we have 65 + 1 = 66"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 379,
	"Question" : "What is 79 + 9 X 5 - 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy-nine plus nine times five minus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 115,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and fifteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 431,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by five and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 5 and 9 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 79 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 5 = 45; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have: 79 + 45 - 9; 79 + 45 = 124; Now we have: 124 - 9 = 115"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 380,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 6 X (1 + 7) + 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus six times (one plus seven) plus two?", 
	"Answer" : 58,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 114,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by the sum of one and seven before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 and 7, and multiply 6 by that sum. Then add 8 to that product, and then add 2 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 7 = 8; Now we have: 8 + 6 X 8 + 2;  6 X 8 = 48; Now we have: 8 + 48 + 2; 8 + 48 = 56; Now we have 56 + 2 = 58"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 381,
	"Question" : "What is 59 + 7 X 6 - 9 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is fifty-nine plus seven times six minus nine times three?", 
	"Answer" : 74,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 369,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by six and nine by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 6 and 9 by 3, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 59 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 6 = 42; 9 X 3 = 27; Now we have: 59 + 42 - 27; 59 + 42 = 101; Now we have: 101 - 27 = 74"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 382,
	"Question" : "What is (4 + 7) X 4 - 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (four plus seven) times four minus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 35,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 35,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by one before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 and 7, and multiply 4 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 9 and 1 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 7 = 11; Now we have: 11 X 4 - 9 X 1; 11 X 4 = 44; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have: 44 - 9 = 35"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 383,
	"Question" : "What is 72 + 7 X 6 - 5 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy-two plus seven times six minus five times four?", 
	"Answer" : 94,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 454,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by six and five by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 6 and 5 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 72 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 6 = 42; 5 X 4 = 20; Now we have: 72 + 42 - 20; 72 + 42 = 114; Now we have: 114 - 20 = 94"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 384,
	"Question" : "What is (5 + 9) X 3 - 9 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (five plus nine) times three minus nine times two?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 66,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by two before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 and 9, and multiply 3 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 9 and 2 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 9 = 14; Now we have: 14 X 3 - 9 X 2; 14 X 3 = 42; 9 X 2 = 18; Now we have: 42 - 18 = 24"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 385,
	"Question" : "What is 27 + 6 X 6 - 8 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is twenty-seven plus six times six minus eight times two?", 
	"Answer" : 47,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 182,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by six and eight by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 6 and 8 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 27 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 6 = 36; 8 X 2 = 16; Now we have: 27 + 36 - 16; 27 + 36 = 63; Now we have: 63 - 16 = 47"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 386,
	"Question" : "What is (7 + 6) X 4 - 7 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (seven plus six) times four minus seven times two?", 
	"Answer" : 38,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 90,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by two before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 7 and 6, and multiply 4 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 7 and 2 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 + 6 = 13; Now we have: 13 X 4 - 7 X 2; 13 X 4 = 52; 7 X 2 = 14; Now we have: 52 - 14 = 38"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 387,
	"Question" : "What is 70 + 8 X 6 - 5 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy plus eight times six minus five times four?", 
	"Answer" : 98,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 448,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by six and five by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 6 and 5 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 70 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 6 = 48; 5 X 4 = 20; Now we have: 70 + 48 - 20; 70 + 48 = 118; Now we have: 118 - 20 = 98"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 388,
	"Question" : "What is (5 + 8) X 1 - 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (five plus eight) times one minus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 13,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is thirteen.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by zero before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 5 and 8, and multiply 1 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 8 and 0 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 + 8 = 13; Now we have: 13 X 1 - 8 X 0; 13 X 1 = 13; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 13 - 0 = 13"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 389,
	"Question" : "What is 94 + 6 X 7 - 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is ninety-four plus six times seven minus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 136,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and thirty-six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 700,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by seven and eight by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 7 and 8 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 94 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 7 = 42; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 94 + 42 - 0; 94 + 42 = 136; Now we have: 136 - 0 = 136"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 390,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 5 X (2 + 8) + 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus five times (two plus eight) plus two?", 
	"Answer" : 58,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 112,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by the sum of two and eight before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 and 8, and multiply 5 by that sum. Then add 6 to that product, and then add 2 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 8 = 10; Now we have: 6 + 5 X 10 + 2;  5 X 10 = 50; Now we have: 6 + 50 + 2; 6 + 50 = 56; Now we have 56 + 2 = 58"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 391,
	"Question" : "What is 46 + 7 X 7 - 5 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is forty-six plus seven times seven minus five times four?", 
	"Answer" : 75,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 351,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by seven and five by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 7 and 5 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 46 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 7 = 49; 5 X 4 = 20; Now we have: 46 + 49 - 20; 46 + 49 = 95; Now we have: 95 - 20 = 75"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 392,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 6 X (4 + 6) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus six times (four plus six) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 65,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 74,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by the sum of four and six before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 4 and 6, and multiply 6 by that sum. Then add 1 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "4 + 6 = 10; Now we have: 1 + 6 X 10 + 4;  6 X 10 = 60; Now we have: 1 + 60 + 4; 1 + 60 = 61; Now we have 61 + 4 = 65"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 393,
	"Question" : "What is 50 + 6 X 7 - 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is fifty plus six times seven minus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 92,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 392,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by seven and eight by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 7 and 8 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 50 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 7 = 42; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 50 + 42 - 0; 50 + 42 = 92; Now we have: 92 - 0 = 92"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 394,
	"Question" : "What is 1 + 6 X (3 + 5) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is one plus six times (three plus five) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 53,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 60,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by the sum of three and five before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 and 5, and multiply 6 by that sum. Then add 1 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 5 = 8; Now we have: 1 + 6 X 8 + 4;  6 X 8 = 48; Now we have: 1 + 48 + 4; 1 + 48 = 49; Now we have 49 + 4 = 53"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 395,
	"Question" : "What is 27 + 6 X 6 - 6 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is twenty-seven plus six times six minus six times two?", 
	"Answer" : 51,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 186,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by six and six by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 6 by 6 and 6 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 27 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 X 6 = 36; 6 X 2 = 12; Now we have: 27 + 36 - 12; 27 + 36 = 63; Now we have: 63 - 12 = 51"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 396,
	"Question" : "What is (3 + 8) X 4 - 9 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (three plus eight) times four minus nine times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 44,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 0,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by zero before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 3 and 8, and multiply 4 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 9 and 0 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "3 + 8 = 11; Now we have: 11 X 4 - 9 X 0; 11 X 4 = 44; 9 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 44 - 0 = 44"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 397,
	"Question" : "What is 23 + 9 X 8 - 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is twenty-three plus nine times eight minus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 95,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 256,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by eight and eight by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 8 and 8 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 23 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 8 = 72; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 23 + 72 - 0; 23 + 72 = 95; Now we have: 95 - 0 = 95"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 398,
	"Question" : "What is 5 + 8 X (1 + 8) + 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is five plus eight times (one plus eight) plus one?", 
	"Answer" : 78,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 118,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by the sum of one and eight before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 and 8, and multiply 8 by that sum. Then add 5 to that product, and then add 1 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 8 = 9; Now we have: 5 + 8 X 9 + 1;  8 X 9 = 72; Now we have: 5 + 72 + 1; 5 + 72 = 77; Now we have 77 + 1 = 78"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 399,
	"Question" : "What is 62 + 8 X 8 - 7 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is sixty-two plus eight times eight minus seven times two?", 
	"Answer" : 112,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and twelve.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 546,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by eight and seven by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 8 and 7 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 62 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 8 = 64; 7 X 2 = 14; Now we have: 62 + 64 - 14; 62 + 64 = 126; Now we have: 126 - 14 = 112"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 400,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 6 X (2 + 7) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus six times (two plus seven) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 65,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 121,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by the sum of two and seven before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 and 7, and multiply 6 by that sum. Then add 7 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 7 = 9; Now we have: 7 + 6 X 9 + 4;  6 X 9 = 54; Now we have: 7 + 54 + 4; 7 + 54 = 61; Now we have 61 + 4 = 65"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 401,
	"Question" : "What is 76 + 9 X 6 - 6 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seventy-six plus nine times six minus six times four?", 
	"Answer" : 106,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and six.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 486,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by six and six by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 9 by 6 and 6 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 76 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "9 X 6 = 54; 6 X 4 = 24; Now we have: 76 + 54 - 24; 76 + 54 = 130; Now we have: 130 - 24 = 106"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 402,
	"Question" : "What is 3 + 7 X (0 + 8) + 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is three plus seven times (zero plus eight) plus one?", 
	"Answer" : 60,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 81,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by the sum of zero and eight before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 8, and multiply 7 by that sum. Then add 3 to that product, and then add 1 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 8 = 8; Now we have: 3 + 7 X 8 + 1;  7 X 8 = 56; Now we have: 3 + 56 + 1; 3 + 56 = 59; Now we have 59 + 1 = 60"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 403,
	"Question" : "What is 96 + 7 X 6 - 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is ninety-six plus seven times six minus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 129,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and twenty-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 609,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by six and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 6 and 9 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 96 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 6 = 42; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have: 96 + 42 - 9; 96 + 42 = 138; Now we have: 138 - 9 = 129"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 404,
	"Question" : "What is 9 + 6 X (1 + 9) + 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is nine plus six times (one plus nine) plus one?", 
	"Answer" : 70,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 151,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply six by the sum of one and nine before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 and 9, and multiply 6 by that sum. Then add 9 to that product, and then add 1 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 9 = 10; Now we have: 9 + 6 X 10 + 1;  6 X 10 = 60; Now we have: 9 + 60 + 1; 9 + 60 = 69; Now we have 69 + 1 = 70"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 405,
	"Question" : "What is 34 + 5 X 9 - 9 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is thirty-four plus five times nine minus nine times four?", 
	"Answer" : 43,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 315,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by nine and nine by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 9 and 9 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 34 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 9 = 45; 9 X 4 = 36; Now we have: 34 + 45 - 36; 34 + 45 = 79; Now we have: 79 - 36 = 43"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 406,
	"Question" : "What is 7 + 9 X (1 + 7) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is seven plus nine times (one plus seven) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 83,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 132,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by the sum of one and seven before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 1 and 7, and multiply 9 by that sum. Then add 7 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "1 + 7 = 8; Now we have: 7 + 9 X 8 + 4;  9 X 8 = 72; Now we have: 7 + 72 + 4; 7 + 72 = 79; Now we have 79 + 4 = 83"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 407,
	"Question" : "What is 53 + 8 X 6 - 8 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is fifty-three plus eight times six minus eight times one?", 
	"Answer" : 93,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is ninety-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 358,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by six and eight by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 6 and 8 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 53 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 6 = 48; 8 X 1 = 8; Now we have: 53 + 48 - 8; 53 + 48 = 101; Now we have: 101 - 8 = 93"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 408,
	"Question" : "What is (6 + 8) X 3 - 9 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (six plus eight) times three minus nine times two?", 
	"Answer" : 24,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is twenty-four.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 66,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by two before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 6 and 8, and multiply 3 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 9 and 2 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "6 + 8 = 14; Now we have: 14 X 3 - 9 X 2; 14 X 3 = 42; 9 X 2 = 18; Now we have: 42 - 18 = 24"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 409,
	"Question" : "What is 43 + 5 X 9 - 5 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is forty-three plus five times nine minus five times four?", 
	"Answer" : 68,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 412,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by nine and five by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 9 and 5 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 43 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 9 = 45; 5 X 4 = 20; Now we have: 43 + 45 - 20; 43 + 45 = 88; Now we have: 88 - 20 = 68"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 410,
	"Question" : "What is 2 + 9 X (0 + 6) + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is two plus nine times (zero plus six) plus three?", 
	"Answer" : 59,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-nine.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 69,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply nine by the sum of zero and six before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 6, and multiply 9 by that sum. Then add 2 to that product, and then add 3 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 6 = 6; Now we have: 2 + 9 X 6 + 3;  9 X 6 = 54; Now we have: 2 + 54 + 3; 2 + 54 = 56; Now we have 56 + 3 = 59"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 411,
	"Question" : "What is 92 + 8 X 7 - 9 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is ninety-two plus eight times seven minus nine times three?", 
	"Answer" : 121,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is one hundred and twenty-one.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 673,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by seven and nine by three",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 7 and 9 by 3, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 92 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 7 = 56; 9 X 3 = 27; Now we have: 92 + 56 - 27; 92 + 56 = 148; Now we have: 148 - 27 = 121"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 412,
	"Question" : "What is (0 + 8) X 3 - 7 X 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (zero plus eight) times three minus seven times three?", 
	"Answer" : 3,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 51,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by three before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 8, and multiply 3 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 7 and 3 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 8 = 8; Now we have: 8 X 3 - 7 X 3; 8 X 3 = 24; 7 X 3 = 21; Now we have: 24 - 21 = 3"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 413,
	"Question" : "What is 36 + 7 X 8 - 7 X 2?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is thirty-six plus seven times eight minus seven times two?", 
	"Answer" : 78,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is seventy-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 330,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by eight and seven by two",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 7 by 8 and 7 by 2, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 36 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "7 X 8 = 56; 7 X 2 = 14; Now we have: 36 + 56 - 14; 36 + 56 = 92; Now we have: 92 - 14 = 78"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 414,
	"Question" : "What is 6 + 7 X (0 + 8) + 3?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is six plus seven times (zero plus eight) plus three?", 
	"Answer" : 65,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 107,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply seven by the sum of zero and eight before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 0 and 8, and multiply 7 by that sum. Then add 6 to that product, and then add 3 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "0 + 8 = 8; Now we have: 6 + 7 X 8 + 3;  7 X 8 = 56; Now we have: 6 + 56 + 3; 6 + 56 = 62; Now we have 62 + 3 = 65"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 415,
	"Question" : "What is 35 + 5 X 9 - 8 X 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is thirty-five plus five times nine minus eight times four?", 
	"Answer" : 48,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is forty-eight.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 328,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by nine and eight by four",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 9 and 8 by 4, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 35 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 9 = 45; 8 X 4 = 32; Now we have: 35 + 45 - 32; 35 + 45 = 80; Now we have: 80 - 32 = 48"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 416,
	"Question" : "What is 8 + 5 X (2 + 9) + 4?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is eight plus five times (two plus nine) plus four?", 
	"Answer" : 67,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-seven.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 147,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by the sum of two and nine before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 2 and 9, and multiply 5 by that sum. Then add 8 to that product, and then add 4 to that sum",
		"Written General Feedback" : "2 + 9 = 11; Now we have: 8 + 5 X 11 + 4;  5 X 11 = 55; Now we have: 8 + 55 + 4; 8 + 55 = 63; Now we have 63 + 4 = 67"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 417,
	"Question" : "What is 22 + 8 X 5 - 8 X 0?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is twenty-two plus eight times five minus eight times zero?", 
	"Answer" : 62,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is sixty-two.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 150,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply eight by five and eight by zero",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 8 by 5 and 8 by 0, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 22 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 X 5 = 40; 8 X 0 = 0; Now we have: 22 + 40 - 0; 22 + 40 = 62; Now we have: 62 - 0 = 62"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 418,
	"Question" : "What is (8 + 7) X 4 - 5 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is (eight plus seven) times four minus five times one?", 
	"Answer" : 55,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is fifty-five.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 55,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by one before you do any subtraction",
		"Written Explanation" : "Add 8 and 7, and multiply 4 by that sum. Then subtract the product of 5 and 1 from that product",
		"Written General Feedback" : "8 + 7 = 15; Now we have: 15 X 4 - 5 X 1; 15 X 4 = 60; 5 X 1 = 5; Now we have: 60 - 5 = 55"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Parentheses", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 },

 {
	"QuestionID" : 419,
	"Question" : "What is 67 + 5 X 5 - 9 X 1?",
	"Spoken Question" : "What is sixty-seven plus five times five minus nine times one?", 
	"Answer" : 83,
	"Spoken Answer" : "The correct answer is eighty-three.",
	"Mistakes" : {
		"Common Mistake 1" : 351,
		"Spoken Explanation 1" : " Remember to do multiplication first! So multiply five by five and nine by one",
		"Written Explanation" : "Multiply 5 by 5 and 9 by 1, and subtract the second product from the first. Then, add 67 to that difference",
		"Written General Feedback" : "5 X 5 = 25; 9 X 1 = 9; Now we have: 67 + 25 - 9; 67 + 25 = 92; Now we have: 92 - 9 = 83"
	},
	"Difficulty Level" : 3,
	"Problem Type" : "Multiplication", 
	"Max Time" : 60
 }
]
